本字幕由「泉水渗透进字幕组」制作
■
翻译&时轴：yojoU      听写：Whisper      压制：FFmpeg
「学间休息」第 1 集
停 止 动 脑
好了  我们得学间休息90秒钟
Okay, we have to take a 90-second study break.
90秒整?
90 seconds?
我看过一项研究  说大脑只能持续学习36分钟
I read a study that says the brain can only learn for 36 minutes
然后需要休息90秒
and then it needs to rest for 90 seconds.
行
Okay.
你啥时候看的
When did you read this study?
上一次休息期间
During our last break.
那你怎么知道要休息?
Then how did you learn it?
好吧 我...
Well, I...
休息时不能动脑!
Stop using your brains!
你们想帮我研究一下我一直在塑造的角色吗
You guys want to help me with the character I've been workshopping?
没时间等你们回答了
No time for an answer.
还有时间吗  呃...
Is there enough time left to, uh...
哦 见鬼 我憋不住了
Oh, heck, I'm going for it.
你们看
You guys...
阿布蒂的大脑好像关机了
I think we killed Abed.
如果我不小心花了最后10秒钟思考西班牙语...
So if I accidentally spend the last 10 seconds thinking about Spanish...
想都别想
Don't even joke about that.
怎么回事
What happened?
中途我意识到时间可能来不及了
I realized halfway there I'd never make it in time.
安妮  瞧你做的好事
Annie, look what you're doing to people.
时间表里已经安排了上厕所的时间
Bathroom breaks are already built into the schedule.
看到了吗  在乌龟这
See? The turtle's?
我可以憋到乌龟这
I can hold it until the turtle.
我叫詹姆斯
My name's James.
詹姆斯·不列颠
James British.
我喜欢把马提尼酒搅拌摇匀
I like my martinis stirred and shaken.
你好  佩妮 佩妮
Yes, Penny, Penny.
佩妮小姐  有何贵干
Miss Penny Penny, yes.
系列喜剧电影《王牌大贱谍》的主角
你演的是奥斯汀·鲍尔斯?
Austin Powers?
那是谁
Who?
三  二  一
Three, two, one.
哦  到时间了
Oh, time's up.
可以继续学习了
Back to studying.
遥遥领先
Way ahead of you.
「学间休息」 第 2 集
真 心 话 大 冒 险
好了  90秒学间休息
All right, 90 seconds study break.
虽然很不想这么说
I never say this, so...
感谢学间休息的力量
appreciate its power.
我们不能继续学习吗
Can't we just keep studying?
我们快学完了
I mean, we're almost done,
我们的校园安全取决于阿布蒂能否上柔道课
and our campus safety depends on Abed making his judo class.
杰夫  休息时间很重要
Jeff, these breaks are important.
它让我们的头脑保持清醒
They keep our brains fresh.
我们可以玩个游戏
We could play a game.
行吧
Fine.
特洛伊  真心话还是大冒险
Troy, truth or dare?
真心话
Truth.
你不介意吧
Would you?
也许她得剪个头发
Maybe she got a haircut
再减少点控制欲
and a less controlling personality.
你俩给我走开
Guys move off it.
好的
Okay.
阿布蒂  真心话还是大冒险
Abed, truth or dare?
大冒险
Dare.
教我一个很酷的空手道招式
Tease me a cool karate move.
握住我的手腕
Attack my wrist.
握住另一个  用另一只手
Other wrist, with the other hand.
别看我的表情
Don't look me in the face.
皮尔斯 真心话或大冒险
Pierce, truth or dare?
真心话
Truth.
不要!
NOOOOOO!
不好意思
Sorry.
你们继续
Go ahead.
有什么让你感到羞耻的事吗
What's something you're ashamed of?
没有!
No!
抱歉  请继续
Sorry, go ahead.
在昨晚的问答比赛里
During trivia last night,
我答错了一道题  导致我们队输了比赛
I answered a question wrong and it cost my team the game.
就这?
That's it?
嗯
Yep.
原来
Turns out...
*uvula*：悬雍垂  俗称小舌头  当张开口发出"啊"音的时候能看到
此处可能引用了切维在《周六夜现场》上的小品<Babs' Uvula>
你的小舌在你嘴里
your uvula is in your mouth.
我也有一个
I have one too.
在我嘴里
It's in my mouth.
好了  继续学习
All right, back to studying.
好
Okay.
[S03E21]  Troy被空调维修学院带走前 Britta给了他一缕自己的秀发
也许剪个头发就行
Maybe just a haircut.
「学间休息」 第 3 集
代  沟
学间休息时间到
Study break time!
花90秒放松一下
Take 90 seconds and relax.
本剧首次出现熔岩游戏（非正式）
快起来  地面现在是熔岩
Quick, the floor is lava!
有人打牌吗
Anyone for pinochle?
算我一个
I'll play.
真有趣
Interesting.
怎么了
What?
代沟正在分裂我们的小组
The generation gap is splitting our group.
布雷塔  地面可是岩浆啊
Britta, the floor is lava!
而你正好夹在两代人中间
And you're right in the middle of it.
要我给你发牌吗  布雷塔
Britta, am I dealing you in?
哦呜  岩浆太可怕了
Oooooh, lava~
熔岩游戏怎样才算赢
The floor is lava. How do you win?
通常你只需跳到安全的地方
Usually you just jump to safety.
片中的怪物藏在地下通过震动定位  人们只能呆在屋顶和岩石上
我们在这呆着不动的样子更像电影《异形魔怪》
But since we're straining here, this is more like the movie Tremors.
震颤是啥
Well, what is Tremors?
你再这么说  我就要加入熔岩世代了
You keep talking like that, I'm moving to the lava generation.
我不玩了
I'm out.
现实太没意思了
The reality's blown.
可惜这些躺在地上的老年人没被沙虫吃掉
With all these old people on the ground not getting devoured by sandworms.
沙虫又是啥  我不懂
Sandworms? I don't understand.
小屁孩的玩意儿  别理他们
They're kids. Ignore them.
把注意力放在我这
Pay attention to me.
成熟点吧  老古董
Grow up, Oldie-Von-Moldy.
大家别吵了
Guys, let's not fight.
安妮  你为了买那瓶3美元的水  路过了几个饮水机?
Annie, how many water fountains did you pass by to buy that three-dollars-water?
这可是液压强化水
It's hydraulically fortified.
皮尔斯
Pierce
你旅行时是怎么导航的?
When you travel, how do you navigate?
靠我车后备箱满满的地图册
With my trunk full of atlases?
问题的关键是  愚蠢不分年龄
Point is, stupidity comes in all ages,
尤其是在学习西语时
especially when it comes to Spanish,
该词首次出现在 S01E02 片尾  Troy和Abed的西语rap
除了 biblioteca 这个词我们啥都不会说
which none of us can speak beyond the word biblioteca.
所以  我们能不能...
So can we please...
时间到  大家开始学习
Time's up. Everyone study.
谢天谢地
Thank you.
刚才皮尔斯说的纸牌游戏 Pinochle
小便指关节
Pee-knuckle.
撒尿  指节
Pee-   knuckle.
尿关节
Peeknuckle.
从指关节里尿出来
Ima pee out of my knuckle.